Sobriety
Yes! So I'm home!
I'm home!
The kitchen is so clean!
I would like to show you the ingredients we bought!
Yay!
Low fat beef!
We have beef, pork, ground beef, meat, pork, cheese, curry, yogurt, ice cream, gum syrup, onions, sweet potatoes, apples, broccoli!
Yes!
Look forward to seeing what we can make!
Enjoy!
Wait, who is that guy!
Who is that guy?
I just put three of them together.
My Yamatoko is here.
The onions are for hamburgers!
I've always dreamed of cooking together like this.
It's something I want to do before I die.
That's good! Heart!
That's good! Look at this!
It's a heart!
I've never done that before.
It's so cute!
I could win this.
Listen to this!
I realized in the car that I didn't buy breadcrumbs and eggs.
I can't make hamburgers.
My eyes hurt.
When I'm cutting it, it's fine, but when it's cooked and fluffy, it hurts!
I did college for the meat.
I put water in the pan before putting the meat in
Hamburgers please!
Lassi might be a bit of a problem
This isn't enough, we can all make curry.
I should at least make a whole portion of yogurt.
Isn't it tender?
It doesn't look good here.
Smudge?
That's the end of that thing!
Listen to me!
Go away.
Lassie might be in a bit of trouble.
Here it is.
I'm definitely going for the chocolate.
It's done!
Oh, my God, I did it!
I'll see you guys later.
It's the last one we're all going to buy.
I'm sure this one will be a winner.
Let's go for it.
Thanks, guys.
I couldn't have done it without you guys.
Well, have fun.
See you later. See you later.
Bye bye.
Yay!
I'm back from Worst Wisdom.
I'm back.
I'd like to introduce you to what I've got for you.
Medium hot and sweet
Chicken
Onions and potatoes
Cheese
Potato chips
Rice balls
Naan!
We want to make a curry with naan this time
Cheese and curry!
Yay!
I think it's good. I think it's good.
Ready?
All right, let's get started.
You mean you've only made minced meat?
Maybe I've never used a knife.
Really?
Really? Hold on.
I've never used a knife at all.
Are you sure about that?
He said it's dangerous to be a chef.
I'm afraid he's going to kill me.
What?
It's my first time cutting with a knife.
Let's get started.
I'm scared.
I'm scared
Yes, I'm afraid.
I succeeded in cutting with a kitchen knife for the first time!
I'm glad I stood up for the first time in the new year
Then, Yuna, please
I'm counting on you
I'll return the extra 50 yen.
I'll give you back one potato
I'll give you back one potato.
Onions?
Because I don't need onions anymore.
Okay, I'll give you back the onion.
I'll give you back the onion.
Can you take this?
Can you take this?Can you hold this?
You want onions?
Yeah, we'll put them in together.
So you can make one for each of you?
One at a time, like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You mix them together.
In the same pot.
I see.
Saute onions.
It's already almost in the pot.
Today's lunch
All together
How did I get hit by something?
Worst
Curry is ready!
Yay!
We did our best
I'll show you the finished product later
I'd like to show it to the members when I show it to them.
I'd like to heat this up at that time.
I'd like to do that.
I hope you all enjoy it.
Enjoy!
I'll show you the finished product later.
Yay!
Ta-da!
It's done!
Then, I'll introduce the potato chips.
Here you go!
Milk.
Frog.
Potatoes.
Miner.
Cheese
Salad chips consommé flavor
Consomme. Important.
Mini chocolate
Oshima's
Almond cheese
Yay
Misako
It looks like we went over our budget by 1,000 yen.
How much over?
190 yen.
Then give up the 190 yen.
What should we do?
Potato chips.
Potatoes.
I'll take a potato chip.
Bye-bye.
It's all at once.
Two at once.
Shut up.
Okay, I'll do it.
Let's do it!
Let's go!
We're going to divide this into lots.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Oh! You got it!
Oh! He's got it!
He's got it!
He's eating chips.
I put roux, milk, water, salt and pepper.
Looks delicious.
It's my first time cooking. I don't know how it'll turn out.
Don't worry, I'll figure it out in the edit.
What?
It tastes good.
To the left.
It glows.
Love is everything
Dancing?
Dancing.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna put in some barley tea powder.
Yeah, I'm nervous.
I'm not doing anything.
Isn't it good?
Moey-moey.
Welcome back, sweetie.
Nothing's going on.
Did you get it?
Nothing.
I know, right?
It's done.
I did my best.
So, how do you feel?
I don't have it yet, but I'd like to unveil it with all the other teams later!
Yay!
Enjoy the show!
The products here are the curry of the pigs' team!
And yet, the pig team was the most expensive, at 3,000 yen!
This will be the lassi suggested by Hinano-san!
But I haven't tasted it, it's delicious!But I didn't taste it, it's delicious!
I eat and stuff properly!
By the way, I didn't taste this one either.
Tasting the brain!
Again, I'm trying to give a maximum of 30 points per team for taste, originality, and miracles.
If miracles are hard to convey, please explain them to the people eating!
Cheers!
Delicious!
Good!
Hinano-san's lassi!
Then match it!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's sweet and tasty!
Really?
It's a miracle!
What's a miracle? Maybe you didn't use any meat?
I thought it would be better with a hamburger steak, so I added pirico.
I forgot the egg and eggs when I was in the car.
So I didn't use them.
What?
Who made the hamburgers?
Did you do it?
All-fi.
Oh, hamburgers.
I did it!
I made a lassi!
Now, I'd like to ask each team to decide the score.
Taste, Originality and Miracle
Eh, this is difficult.
Please tell them the score in order.
Okay, let's start with the flavor.
Six points!
Wow!
Ten points!
Yay!
Oh, my God, that's one, and you're the one.
Like you're the one who's terrible.
Okay, next. Originality.
Seven points!
Oh, wow!
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
8 points!
Oh!
Last but not least, the python.
Seven points!
Oh!
Five!
That's a 5 out of 3.
Eight points.
Five points.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
I'm continuing like this more than I thought I would.
I was surprised.
Okay, next.
First of all, the kiseki is a hamburger steak.
It's amazing that they can even handle the drinks.
The three of us can afford it.
That's right.
Does the hamburger steak have more meat in it?
Yes.
It's like there's more meat in it.
Couldn't you buy meat?
Ehhhhh!
I hear you smiling.
When the team of three went to the meat section...
Not at all.
We have money, so if we buy all the meat for the curry...
If we buy all the meat for the curry, won't we be able to buy for the next team?
Aah!
I'll give you 5 points for that.
I'll take four.
Wait a minute, we're going to have to discuss this.
Ehhhhh!
Eh, but that's the guy who lent it to you.
That's right.
That's one way, isn't it?
You can do that.
Victim.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Please take care of it.
Yay!
The duck team is ready!
what is this?
My curry is...
First of all, I used beef!
Chicken curry is the best curry, isn't it?
So I used chicken, not pork or beef!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
The most amazing thing about this dish is that
Shinju-chan used a knife for the first time in her life!Shinju-chan used a knife for the first time in her life!
It's an aligo.
ta-da!
I'm curious
Asahi is famous for its o-hagi (rice balls)
but this o-hagi is originality!
I had a little taste
What did I get?
He said he ate it!
You're going to taste the raw meat?
I have to eat it before serving it to everyone.
I thought I had to taste it before serving it to everyone.
So I did.
One for everyone?
Yes, we did.
We ate quite a lot.
That was the curry of the duck class.
It was delicious!
Now let's hear the scores from the teams.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Eight.
Next is originality
And finally, miracles
It was so good.
It was delicious.
The taste is beyond reproach.
I have no complaints about it
Each to their own
I have to do this
I was thankful for a well-cooked meal
Oh!
It was perfect.
Yes, staff.
Thank you very much.
Yes! We are the last pair!
Congratulations!
We made curry doria!
Amazing.
What? What? Wow!
Well, we couldn't buy breadcrumbs.
So I got you some snacks with almonds in them instead.
All of it?
Yeah, just take it all apart.
Break up the side dish.
And break up the almonds.
Like breadcrumbs.
I mixed the leftover cheese into the roux.
I made a dessert with barley chocolate and marshmallows
Oh, my God!
Are you a staff member?
Yes, yes, I'm a member of your staff.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
I'm sorry, I'm a little nervous.
Delicious.
What's that carrot you just ate?
Potatoes.
Potatoes?
Not cheese?
Curry?
The potatoes are too big.
Hey, that's...
It's a roux.
It's good.
Yum! Potatoes!
The way you put this together is really bad!
I'm sorry.
I don't know why you're making me do such a bad thing.
Oh, well...
I bought everything.
Yeah, right.
No, no, no, no, no.
Delicious!
Okay, let's see how many points each team has discussed.
Let's hear the points for each team.
One to 10!
Six!
Originality
8!
Miracle at the end
10!
It's rude to say that for $1,000, you can draw a wall first.
Desert mark
You did a great job.
I'll have one then.
Delicious!
All three teams got a score.All three teams got a score.
There are so many penalties.
I will start with the second place.
The opposite.
Second place goes to...
With 46 points...
Oh, hilchin'!
That's great!
Good!
I might be in first place!
I think I might be first!
Hey!
With 54 points, first place goes to...
Penguin team wins!
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
It's so frustrating.
But I guess it means we can get closer.
What part of penguins don't sleep?
Which of the penguins won't sleep?
Bubba's team from Billi's team...
All the plates here.
Please clean up.
Let's do it again!
One meal per person this time?
What?
Wait a minute.
Wow.
Please?
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it.
We'll clean up.
We'll eat.
Clean up.
I remember the first time we cleaned this up.
Today.
This is exactly what's going to happen to all of us.
We're all doomed if we get carried away.
That's right.
I don't mind washing dishes.
But from the angle of view, it's no fun if you don't do it at last.
Oh, no!
What's the matter?
No, no, no, no!
I just hate washing dishes
I hate washing dishes
I prefer cooking
Subtitles for this video were created by viewers.